Muhammad Alkautsar Virzawan

SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER



WORK EXPERIENCE

Allianz Indonesia

2020 - Present

Software Quality Assurance Engineer

- Develop and implement web frontend automation testing with Robot Framework Selenium Library and Browser Library
- Develop and implement backend automation testing with Serenity BDD Framework and Rest Assured
- Develop and implement performance testing with JMeter
- Integrating Automated Testing with Jenkins
- Perform manual testing and create a detailed bugs reporting with Jira
- Working in Scrum/Agile development methodologies

Wirecard Technologies Indonesia

2019 - 2020

Software Quality Assurance Engineer

- Develop and implement web frontend automation testing with Serenity BDD Framework using Selenium with Kotlin language
- Develop and implement backend automation testing with Serenity BDD Framework and Rest Assured
- Perform manual testing and create a detailed bugs reporting with Jira
- Working in Scrum/Agile development methodologies

PROFILE

I'm a certified Software Quality Assurance with a demonstrated history of working in the financial and insurance industry for more than 3+ years experience.

Specialized in web frontend and backend automation testing using multiple framework, creating detailed test cases and bug reporting.

EDUCATION

Diponegoro University

Computer Engineering 2014-2018 GPA: 3,29

CERTIFICATION

ISTQB Certified Tester, Foundation Level 2021

CONTACT

0822 9922 9052

ochank255@yahoo.com

www.starvedgeek.com